"Why?"
[AI] “为什么？”
"Why?" is a question
[AI] “为什么？”这是一个问题
that parents ask me all the time.
[AI] 父母总是问我。
"Why did my child develop autism?"
[AI] “为什么我的孩子会患孤独症？”
As a pediatrician. as a geneticist. as a researcher.
[AI] 作为一名儿科医生。作为遗传学家。作为一名研究人员。
we try and address that question.
[AI] 我们试图解决这个问题。
But autism is not a single condition.
[AI] 但孤独症并不是一种单一的疾病。
It's actually a spectrum of disorders.
[AI] 这实际上是一系列的紊乱。
a spectrum that ranges. for instance.
[AI] 范围很广的光谱。例如。
from Justin. a 13-year-old boy
[AI] 来自贾斯汀。一个13岁的男孩
who's not verbal. who can't speak.
[AI] 他不会说话。不会说话的人。
who communicates by using an iPad
[AI] 谁用iPad进行交流
to touch pictures to communicate
[AI] 触摸图片进行交流
his thoughts and his concerns.
[AI] 他的思想和关切。
a little boy who. when he gets upset.
[AI] 一个小男孩。当他生气的时候。
will start rocking.
[AI] 会开始摇晃。
and eventually. when he's disturbed enough.
[AI] 最终。当他够不安的时候。
will bang his head to the point
[AI] 会把他的头撞到点子上
that he can actually cut it open and require stitches.
[AI] 他真的可以把它切开需要缝针。
That same diagnosis of autism. though.
[AI] 同样的自闭症诊断。虽然
also applies to Gabriel.
[AI] 也适用于加布里埃尔。
another 13-year-old boy
[AI] 另一个13岁的男孩
who has quite a different set of challenges.
[AI] 世卫组织面临着完全不同的挑战。
He's actually quite remarkably gifted in mathematics.
[AI] 事实上，他在数学方面非常有天赋。
He can multiple three numbers by three numbers
[AI] 他能把三个数乘以三个数
in his head with ease.
[AI] 在他的脑海里轻松地。
yet when it comes to trying to have a conversation.
[AI] 然而，当谈到试图进行对话时。
he has great difficulty.
[AI] 他有很大的困难。
He doesn't make eye contact.
[AI] 他没有眼神交流。
He has difficulty starting a conversation.
[AI] 他很难开始谈话。
feels awkward.
[AI] 感觉很尴尬。
and when he gets nervous.
[AI] 当他紧张的时候。
he actually shuts down.
[AI] 他真的关机了。
Yet both of these boys
[AI] 然而这两个男孩
have the same diagnosis of autism spectrum disorder.
[AI] 对自闭症谱系障碍有相同的诊断。
One of the things that concerns us
[AI] 我们关心的一件事
is whether or not there really is
[AI] 是否真的有
an epidemic of autism.
[AI] 孤独症的流行。
These days. one in 88 children
[AI] 这些天。88个孩子中就有一个
will be diagnosed with autism.
[AI] 将被诊断为自闭症。
and the question is.
[AI] 问题是。
why does this graph look this way?
[AI] 为什么这张图看起来像这样？
Has that number been increasing
[AI] 这个数字在增加吗
dramatically over time?
[AI] 随着时间的推移会有戏剧性的变化吗？
Or is it because we have now started labeling
[AI] 还是因为我们现在已经开始贴标签
individuals with autism.
[AI] 孤独症患者。
simply giving them a diagnosis
[AI] 只是给他们一个诊断
when they were still present there before
[AI] 当他们以前还在那里的时候
yet simply didn't have that label?
[AI] 但根本就没有这个标签？
And in fact. in the late 1980s. the early 1990s.
[AI] 事实上。20世纪80年代末。1990年代初。
legislation was passed
[AI] 立法获得通过
that actually provided individuals with autism
[AI] 这实际上为自闭症患者提供了帮助
with resources. with access to educational materials
[AI] 有资源。获得教育材料
that would help them.
[AI] 这将有助于他们。
With that increased awareness. more parents.
[AI] 随着意识的提高。更多的父母。
more pediatricians. more educators
[AI] 更多的儿科医生。更多的教育者
learned to recognize the features of autism.
[AI] 学会识别自闭症的特征。
As a result of that. more individuals were diagnosed
[AI] 因此,。更多的人被确诊
and got access to the resources they needed.
[AI] 获得了他们需要的资源。
In addition. we've changed our definition over time.
[AI] 此外随着时间的推移，我们改变了定义。
so in fact we've widened the definition of autism.
[AI] 所以事实上我们拓宽了自闭症的定义。
and that accounts for some of
[AI] 这就解释了其中的一些原因
the increased prevalence that we see.
[AI] 我们看到的发病率增加。
The next question everyone wonders is.
[AI] 每个人都想知道的下一个问题是。
what caused autism?
[AI] 是什么导致了自闭症？
And a common misconception
[AI] 还有一个常见的误解
is that vaccines cause autism.
[AI] 疫苗会导致自闭症。
But let me be very clear:
[AI] 但让我非常明确地说：
Vaccines do not cause autism.
[AI] 疫苗不会导致自闭症。
(Applause)
[AI] （掌声）
In fact. the original research study
[AI] 事实上原始研究
that suggested that was the case
[AI] 这表明情况就是这样
was completely fraudulent.
[AI] 这完全是骗人的。
It was actually retracted from the journal Lancet.
[AI] 它实际上是从《柳叶刀》杂志上收回的。
in which it was published.
[AI] 这本书出版的地方。
and that author. a physician.
[AI] 还有那个作者。医生。
had his medical license taken away from him.
[AI] 他的医疗执照被吊销了。
(Applause)
[AI] （掌声）
The Institute of Medicine.
[AI] 医学研究所。
The Centers for Disease Control.
[AI] 疾病控制中心。
have repeatedly investigated this
[AI] 我们已经反复调查了这一点
and there is no credible evidence
[AI] 而且没有可信的证据
that vaccines cause autism.
[AI] 疫苗会导致自闭症。
Furthermore.
[AI] 此外
one of the ingredients in vaccines.
[AI] 疫苗的成分之一。
something called thimerosal.
[AI] 一种叫做硫柳汞的东西。
was thought to be what the cause of autism was.
[AI] 被认为是导致孤独症的原因。
That was actually removed from vaccines
[AI] 这实际上是从疫苗中去除的
in the year 1992.
[AI] 1992年。
and you can see that it really did not have an effect
[AI] 你可以看到它确实没有效果
in what happened with the prevalence of autism.
[AI] 孤独症的流行情况。
So again. there is no evidence
[AI] 再说一遍。没有证据
that this is the answer.
[AI] 这就是答案。
So the question remains. what does cause autism?
[AI] 因此，问题依然存在。什么导致孤独症？
In fact. there's probably not one single answer.
[AI] 事实上可能没有一个答案。
Just as autism is a spectrum.
[AI] 正如孤独症是一个谱系。
there's a spectrum of etiologies.
[AI] 病因有很多种。
a spectrum of causes.
[AI] 一系列原因。
Based on epidemiological data.
[AI] 基于流行病学数据。
we know that one of the causes.
[AI] 我们知道其中一个原因。
or one of the associations. I should say.
[AI] 或者其中一个协会。我应该说。
is advanced paternal age.
[AI] 他父亲年龄大了。
that is. increasing age of the father
[AI] 就是。父亲年龄的增长
at the time of conception.
[AI] 在受孕时。
In addition. another vulnerable
[AI] 此外另一个弱势群体
and critical period in terms of development
[AI] 发展的关键时期
is when the mother is pregnant.
[AI] 是母亲怀孕的时候。
During that period. while the fetal brain is developing.
[AI] 在此期间。当胎儿大脑发育时。
we know that exposure to certain agents
[AI] 我们知道接触某些药剂
can actually increase the risk of autism.
[AI] 实际上会增加患孤独症的风险。
In particular. there's a medication. valproic acid.
[AI] 特别地。有一种药物。丙戊酸。
which mothers with epilepsy sometimes take.
[AI] 患有癫痫的母亲有时会服用。
we know can increase that risk of autism.
[AI] 我们知道这会增加患孤独症的风险。
In addition. there can be some infectious agents
[AI] 此外可能有一些传染源
that can also cause autism.
[AI] 这也会导致自闭症。
And one of the things I'm going to spend
[AI] 我要花的其中一件事
a lot of time focusing on
[AI] 很多时间专注于
are the genes that can cause autism.
[AI] 是导致自闭症的基因。
I'm focusing on this not because genes
[AI] 我之所以关注这一点，不是因为基因
are the only cause of autism.
[AI] 是导致孤独症的唯一原因。
but it's a cause of autism
[AI] 但这是孤独症的一个原因
that we can readily define
[AI] 我们可以很容易地定义
and be able to better understand the biology
[AI] 能够更好地理解生物学
and understand better how the brain works
[AI] 更好地理解大脑是如何工作的
so that we can come up with strategies
[AI] 这样我们才能想出策略
to be able to intervene.
[AI] 能够干预。
One of the genetic factors that we don't understand.
[AI] 我们不了解的遗传因素之一。
however. is the difference that we see
[AI] 然而我们看到的区别是什么
in terms of males and females.
[AI] 就男性和女性而言。
Males are affected four to one compared to females
[AI] 与女性相比，男性受影响的比例为四比一
with autism.
[AI] 患有自闭症。
and we really don't understand what that cause is.
[AI] 我们真的不明白原因是什么。
One of the ways that we can understand
[AI] 我们可以理解的方式之一
that genetics is a factor
[AI] 基因是一个因素
is by looking at something called
[AI] 就是看一个叫做
the concordance rate.
[AI] 一致性比率。
In other words. if one sibling has autism.
[AI] 换句话说。如果一个兄弟姐妹患有自闭症。
what's the probability
[AI] 可能性有多大
that another sibling in that family will have autism?
[AI] 那个家庭的另一个兄弟姐妹会有自闭症？
And we can look in particular
[AI] 我们可以特别看一下
at three types of siblings:
[AI] 在三种类型的兄弟姐妹中：
identical twins.
[AI] 同卵双胞胎。
twins that actually share 100 percent
[AI] 实际上100%共享的双胞胎
of their genetic information
[AI] 他们的基因信息
and shared the same intrauterine environment.
[AI] 并共享相同的宫内环境。
versus fraternal twins.
[AI] 对双胞胎兄弟。
twins that actually share 50 percent
[AI] 双胞胎实际上分享了50%
of their genetic information.
[AI] 他们的基因信息。
versus regular siblings.
[AI] 和正常的兄弟姐妹相比。
brother-sister. sister-sister.
[AI] 兄弟姐妹。姐姐。
also sharing 50 percent of their genetic information.
[AI] 也分享了他们50%的基因信息。
yet not sharing the same intrauterine environment.
[AI] 但不共享相同的宫内环境。
And when you look at those concordance ratios.
[AI] 当你看这些一致性比率时。
one of the striking things that you will see
[AI] 你会看到一件引人注目的事情
is that in identical twins.
[AI] 是同卵双生的吗。
that concordance rate is 77 percent.
[AI] 符合率为77%。
Remarkably. though.
[AI] 非常虽然
it's not 100 percent.
[AI] 这不是百分之百的。
It is not that genes account for all of the risk for autism.
[AI] 基因并不是孤独症风险的全部原因。
but yet they account for a lot of that risk.
[AI] 但他们也承担了很大的风险。
because when you look at fraternal twins.
[AI] 因为当你看到双胞胎兄弟时。
that concordance rate is only 31 percent.
[AI] 这种一致性比率只有31%。
On the other hand. there is a difference
[AI] 另一方面这是有区别的
between those fraternal twins and the siblings.
[AI] 在那些兄弟姐妹和兄弟姐妹之间。
suggesting that there are common exposures
[AI] 表明存在共同的风险敞口
for those fraternal twins
[AI] 为了那些双胞胎兄弟
that may not be shared as commonly
[AI] 这一点可能并不常见
with siblings alone.
[AI] 只有兄弟姐妹。
So this provides some of the data
[AI] 所以这提供了一些数据
that autism is genetic.
[AI] 自闭症是遗传的。
Well. how genetic is it?
[AI] 好它有多遗传？
When we compare it to other conditions
[AI] 当我们将它与其他条件进行比较时
that we're familiar with.
[AI] 我们熟悉的。
things like cancer. heart disease. diabetes.
[AI] 比如癌症。心脏病。糖尿病
in fact. genetics plays a much larger role in autism
[AI] 事实上遗传学在孤独症中起着更大的作用
than it does in any of these other conditions.
[AI] 比其他任何条件下都好。
But with this. that doesn't tell us what the genes are.
[AI] 但是有了这个。这并没有告诉我们基因是什么。
It doesn't even tell us in any one child.
[AI] 它甚至没有告诉我们任何一个孩子的情况。
is it one gene
[AI] 是一个基因吗
or potentially a combination of genes?
[AI] 或者可能是基因的组合？
And so in fact. in some individuals with autism.
[AI] 事实上也是如此。在一些孤独症患者中。
it is genetic!
[AI] 这是遗传的！
That is. that it is one single.
[AI] 就是。这是一个单一的。
powerful. deterministic gene
[AI] 强大的确定性基因
that causes the autism.
[AI] 这导致了自闭症。
However. in other individuals.
[AI] 然而在其他个体中。
it's genetic. that is.
[AI] 这是遗传的。就是。
that it's actually a combination of genes
[AI] 它实际上是基因的组合
in part with the developmental process
[AI] 部分与发展进程有关
that ultimately determines that risk for autism.
[AI] 这最终决定了患孤独症的风险。
We don't know in any one person. necessarily.
[AI] 我们不知道任何一个人的情况。必要地
which of those two answers it is
[AI] 这两个答案是哪一个
until we start digging deeper.
[AI] 直到我们开始深入挖掘。
So the question becomes.
[AI] 所以问题就变成了。
how can we start to identify
[AI] 我们如何开始识别
what exactly those genes are.
[AI] 这些基因到底是什么。
And let me pose something
[AI] 让我摆个姿势
that might not be intuitive.
[AI] 这可能不是直觉。
In certain individuals.
[AI] 在某些人身上。
they can have autism
[AI] 他们可能患有自闭症
for a reason that is genetic
[AI] 因为一个遗传的原因
but yet not because of autism running in the family.
[AI] 但这并不是因为家里有自闭症。
And the reason is because in certain individuals.
[AI] 这是因为在某些人身上。
they can actually have genetic changes or mutations
[AI] 他们实际上可能有基因改变或突变
that are not passed down from the mother
[AI] 不是母亲传下来的
or from the father.
[AI] 或者从父亲那里。
but actually start brand new in them.
[AI] 但事实上，它们是全新的。
mutations that are present
[AI] 存在的突变
in the egg or the sperm
[AI] 是卵子还是精子
at the time of conception
[AI] 受孕时
but have not been passed down
[AI] 但是没有被传下来
generation through generation within the family.
[AI] 一代又一代的家庭成员。
And we can actually use that strategy
[AI] 我们实际上可以使用这种策略
to now understand and to identify
[AI] 现在要理解和识别
those genes causing autism in those individuals.
[AI] 这些基因导致了这些个体的孤独症。
So in fact. at the Simons Foundation.
[AI] 所以事实上。在西蒙斯基金会。
we took 2.600 individuals
[AI] 我们调查了2600人
that had no family history of autism.
[AI] 没有自闭症家族史。
and we took that child and their mother and father
[AI] 我们带走了那个孩子和他们的父母
and used them to try and understand
[AI] 并用它们来试着理解
what were those genes
[AI] 那些基因是什么
causing autism in those cases?
[AI] 在这些情况下导致自闭症？
To do that. we actually had to comprehensively
[AI] 这样做。事实上，我们必须
be able to look at all that genetic information
[AI] 能够看到所有的遗传信息
and determine what those differences were
[AI] 并确定这些差异是什么
between the mother. the father and the child.
[AI] 在母亲之间。父亲和孩子。
In doing so. I apologize.
[AI] 在这样做的过程中。我道歉。
I'm going to use an outdated analogy
[AI] 我要用一个过时的比喻
of encyclopedias rather than Wikipedia.
[AI] 是百科全书而不是维基百科。
but I'm going to do so to try and help make the point
[AI] 但我会这样做，试图帮助你阐明这一点
that as we did this inventory.
[AI] 就像我们做这个清单一样。
we needed to be able to look at
[AI] 我们需要能够看到
massive amounts of information.
[AI] 大量的信息。
Our genetic information is organized
[AI] 我们的基因信息是有组织的
into a set of 46 volumes.
[AI] 共46卷。
and when we did that. we had to be able to account
[AI] 当我们这么做的时候。我们必须能够解释清楚
for each of those 46 volumes.
[AI] 这46卷中的每一卷。
because in some cases with autism.
[AI] 因为在某些情况下自闭症患者。
there's actually a single volume that's missing.
[AI] 实际上有一个卷丢失了。
We had to get more granular than that. though.
[AI] 我们必须得到更多的颗粒。虽然
and so we had to start opening those books.
[AI] 所以我们不得不开始打开那些书。
and in some cases. the genetic change
[AI] 在某些情况下。基因变化
was more subtle.
[AI] 这更微妙。
It might have been a single paragraph that was missing.
[AI] 这可能是缺少的一段。
or yet. even more subtle than that.
[AI] 或者现在。甚至比这更微妙。
a single letter.
[AI] 一封信。
one out of three billion letters
[AI] 三十亿封信中就有一封
that was changed. that was altered.
[AI] 改变了。改变了。
yet had profound effects
[AI] 但却产生了深远的影响
in terms of how the brain functions
[AI] 就大脑的功能而言
and affects behavior.
[AI] 并影响行为。
In doing this within these families.
[AI] 在这些家庭中这样做。
we were able to account for approximately
[AI] 我们能够解释大约
25 percent of the individuals
[AI] 25%的个人
and determine that there was a single
[AI] 并确定有一个
powerful genetic factor
[AI] 强大的遗传因子
that caused autism within those families.
[AI] 这导致了这些家庭中的孤独症。
On the other hand. there's 75 percent
[AI] 另一方面百分之七十五
that we still haven't figured out.
[AI] 我们还没弄明白。
As we did this. though.
[AI] 当我们这样做的时候。虽然
it was really quite humbling.
[AI] 这真是太令人谦卑了。
because we realized that there was not simply
[AI] 因为我们意识到
one gene for autism.
[AI] 孤独症的一个基因。
In fact. the current estimates are
[AI] 事实上目前的估计是：
that there are 200 to 400 different genes
[AI] 有200到400个不同的基因
that can cause autism.
[AI] 那会导致孤独症。
And that explains. in part.
[AI] 这就解释了。部分。
why we see such a broad spectrum
[AI] 为什么我们看到如此广泛的光谱
in terms of its effects.
[AI] 就其影响而言。
Although there are that many genes.
[AI] 虽然有那么多的基因。
there is some method to the madness.
[AI] 有一些方法可以消除这种疯狂。
It's not simply random
[AI] 这不仅仅是随机的
200. 400 different genes.
[AI] 200.400个不同的基因。
but in fact they fit together.
[AI] 但事实上，它们是结合在一起的。
They fit together in a pathway.
[AI] 它们在一条通道中结合在一起。
They fit together in a network
[AI] 它们结合在一起形成一个网络
that's starting to make sense now
[AI] 现在开始有意义了
in terms of how the brain functions.
[AI] 关于大脑的功能。
We're starting to have a bottom-up approach
[AI] 我们开始采用自下而上的方法
where we're identifying those genes.
[AI] 我们在那里识别这些基因。
those proteins. those molecules.
[AI] 那些蛋白质。那些分子。
understanding how they interact together
[AI] 了解它们是如何相互作用的
to make that neuron work.
[AI] 让神经元工作。
understanding how those neurons interact together
[AI] 了解这些神经元是如何相互作用的
to make circuits work.
[AI] 使电路工作。
and understand how those circuits work
[AI] 了解这些电路是如何工作的
to now control behavior.
[AI] 现在控制行为。
and understand that both in individuals with autism
[AI] 并了解自闭症患者
as well as individuals who have normal cognition.
[AI] 以及认知正常的人。
But early diagnosis is a key for us.
[AI] 但早期诊断是我们的关键。
Being able to make that diagnosis
[AI] 能够做出这样的诊断
of someone who's susceptible
[AI] 一个易受影响的人
at a time in a window
[AI] 一次在窗户里
where we have the ability to transform.
[AI] 在那里我们有能力转变。
to be able to impact
[AI] 能够影响
that growing. developing brain is critical.
[AI] 那是在成长。发展大脑至关重要。
And so folks like Ami Klin have developed methods
[AI] 所以像Ami Klin这样的人发明了一些方法
to be able to take infants. small babies.
[AI] 能够带上婴儿。小婴儿。
and be able to use biomarkers.
[AI] 并且能够使用生物标记物。
in this case eye contact and eye tracking.
[AI] 在这种情况下，眼睛接触和眼睛跟踪。
to identify an infant at risk.
[AI] 识别有风险的婴儿。
This particular infant. you can see.
[AI] 这个特别的婴儿。你可以看到。
making very good eye contact with this woman
[AI] 与这位女士进行良好的眼神交流
as she's singing "Itsy. Bitsy Spider."
[AI] 当她唱“Itsy.Bitsy Spider”
in fact is not going to develop autism.
[AI] 事实上，它不会发展成孤独症。
This baby we know is going to be in the clear.
[AI] 我们知道的这个婴儿将被清除。
On the other hand. this other baby
[AI] 另一方面另一个孩子
is going to go on to develop autism.
[AI] 会发展成自闭症。
In this particular child. you can see.
[AI] 在这个特殊的孩子身上。你可以看到。
it's not making good eye contact.
[AI] 这不是很好的眼神交流。
Instead of the eyes focusing in
[AI] 而不是眼睛聚焦在
and having that social connection.
[AI] 还有那种社会关系。
looking at the mouth. looking at the nose.
[AI] 看嘴。看着鼻子。
looking off in another direction.
[AI] 朝另一个方向望去。
but not again socially connecting.
[AI] 但不能再进行社交联系。
and being able to do this on a very large scale.
[AI] 并且能够在非常大的范围内做到这一点。
screen infants. screen children for autism.
[AI] 筛选婴儿。对儿童进行自闭症筛查。
through something very robust. very reliable.
[AI] 通过一些非常强大的东西。非常可靠。
is going to be very helpful to us in terms of being
[AI] 这对我们来说是非常有帮助的
able to intervene at an early stage
[AI] 能够在早期进行干预
when we can have the greatest impact.
[AI] 当我们能够产生最大的影响时。
How are we going to intervene?
[AI] 我们将如何干预？
It's probably going to be a combination of factors.
[AI] 这可能是多种因素综合作用的结果。
In part. in some individuals.
[AI] 部分。在某些人身上。
we're going to try and use medications.
[AI] 我们将尝试使用药物。
And so in fact. identifying the genes for autism
[AI] 事实上也是如此。确定自闭症的基因
is important for us
[AI] 这对我们很重要
to identify drug targets.
[AI] 确定药物靶点。
to identify things that we might be able to impact
[AI] 确定我们可能影响的事情
and can be certain that that's really
[AI] 可以肯定这是真的
what we need to do in autism.
[AI] 我们在孤独症中需要做什么。
But that's not going to be the only answer.
[AI] 但这不是唯一的答案。
Beyond just drugs. we're going to use educational strategies.
[AI] 除了毒品。我们将使用教育策略。
Individuals with autism.
[AI] 孤独症患者。
some of them are wired a little bit differently.
[AI] 他们中的一些人有点不同。
They learn in a different way.
[AI] 他们以不同的方式学习。
They absorb their surroundings in a different way.
[AI] 他们以不同的方式吸收周围的环境。
and we need to be able to educate them
[AI] 我们需要能够教育他们
in a way that serves them best.
[AI] 以最适合他们的方式。
Beyond that. there are a lot of individuals
[AI] 除此之外。有很多个人
in this room who have great ideas
[AI] 在这个房间里谁有好主意
in terms of new technologies we can use.
[AI] 就我们可以使用的新技术而言。
everything from devices we can use to train the brain
[AI] 从我们可以用来训练大脑的各种设备
to be able to make it more efficient
[AI] 能够使它更有效
and to compensate for areas in which
[AI] 以及补偿
it has a little bit of trouble.
[AI] 它有点麻烦。
to even things like Google Glass.
[AI] 甚至谷歌眼镜这样的东西。
You could imagine. for instance. Gabriel.
[AI] 你可以想象。例如。加布里埃尔。
with his social awkwardness.
[AI] 他社交上的笨拙。
might be able to wear Google Glass
[AI] 可能会戴谷歌眼镜
with an earpiece in his ear.
[AI] 耳朵里插着听筒。
and have a coach be able to help him.
[AI] 并且有一个教练能够帮助他。
be able to help think about conversations.
[AI] 能够帮助思考对话。
conversation-starters.
[AI] 对话开始者。
being able to even perhaps one day
[AI] 甚至有一天能够
invite a girl out on a date.
[AI] 邀请一个女孩出去约会。
All of these new technologies
[AI] 所有这些新技术
just offer tremendous opportunities
[AI] 只是提供巨大的机会
for us to be able to impact
[AI] 让我们能够影响
the individuals with autism.
[AI] 孤独症患者。
but yet we have a long way to go.
[AI] 但我们还有很长的路要走。
As much as we know.
[AI] 据我们所知。
there is so much more that we don't know.
[AI] 还有很多我们不知道的。
and so I invite all of you
[AI] 所以我邀请你们所有人
to be able to help us think about
[AI] 能够帮助我们思考
how to do this better.
[AI] 如何做得更好。
to use as a community our collective wisdom
[AI] 将我们的集体智慧用于社区
to be able to make a difference.
[AI] 能够有所作为。
and in particular.
[AI] 尤其是。
for the individuals in families with autism.
[AI] 针对自闭症家庭中的个人。
I invite you to join the interactive autism network.
[AI] 我邀请你加入互动自闭症网络。
to be part of the solution to this.
[AI] 作为解决方案的一部分。
because it's going to take really a lot of us
[AI] 因为这需要我们很多人
to think about what's important.
[AI] 思考什么是重要的。
what's going to be a meaningful difference.
[AI] 这将是一个有意义的区别。
As we think about something
[AI] 当我们思考某事时
that's potentially a solution.
[AI] 这可能是一个解决方案。
how well does it work?
[AI] 效果如何？
Is it something that's really going to make a difference
[AI] 这真的会带来不同吗
in your lives. as an individual.
[AI] 在你的生活中。作为个人。
as a family with autism?
[AI] 作为一个自闭症家庭？
We're going to need individuals of all ages.
[AI] 我们需要不同年龄的人。
from the young to the old.
[AI] 从小到大。
and with all different shapes and sizes
[AI] 有各种不同的形状和大小
of the autism spectrum disorder
[AI] 自闭症谱系障碍的研究
to make sure that we can have an impact.
[AI] 确保我们能产生影响。
So I invite all of you to join the mission
[AI] 所以我邀请你们所有人都加入这个任务
and to help to be able to make the lives
[AI] 并帮助他们创造生活
of individuals with autism
[AI] 孤独症患者
so much better and so much richer.
[AI] 好得多，富得多。
Thank you.
[AI] 非常感谢。
(Applause)
[AI] （掌声）